<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ben Chudyk</title>
    <description>I'm a creative designer with experience in web and print.</description>
    <link>https://benchudyk.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 04:48:58 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 04:48:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Primacoustic</title>
        <description>Acoustic panels for several different industries from home studios to restaurants. Primacoustic is a sister company to Radial Engineering that needed some serious updates. The final product uses wordpress for the CMS. I designed the site and helped with some front end development. I directed the team and reported to the owner for each stage of the process. There was roughly 250 pages and post types full of content so planning was key. We separated products as a post type so that we could manipulate the products for future apps like a room calculator and graphic price list. </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://benchudyk.github.io/web/development/2014/07/18/project-1/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://benchudyk.github.io/web/development/2014/07/18/project-1/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Web</category>
        
        <category>Development</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hafler</title>
        <description>Hafler has a long legacy of power amps for hifi listening systems. The brand was purchased and several new products were developed. The logo was decided but I was in charge of branding and packaging. For the initial 6 products I created box, manuals and other print materials. As well as designed and assisted the development of the site. The website is a static HTML site using LESS and bootstrap for the responsive framework. </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://benchudyk.github.io/web/development/2014/07/17/project-2/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://benchudyk.github.io/web/development/2014/07/17/project-2/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Web</category>
        
        <category>Development</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jensen Transformers</title>
        <description>Another company Radial had purchased to ensure manufacturing for their audio transformers. The original website and brand was re designed. The website was developed with wordpress and bootstrap. I had designed the website and print materials. </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://benchudyk.github.io/web/development/2014/07/16/project-3/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://benchudyk.github.io/web/development/2014/07/16/project-3/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Web</category>
        
        <category>Development</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Radial Engineering</title>
        <description>Radial Engineering is the parent company of several projects I worked on. They are an audio device manufacturer that works with artists all around the world. My job is print and web design for most projects that come through.</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://benchudyk.github.io/web/development/2014/07/15/project-4/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://benchudyk.github.io/web/development/2014/07/15/project-4/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Web</category>
        
        <category>Development</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Industry Workwear</title>
        <description>Industry Workwear is a local retail store that has two locations and wanted an online presence. I worked with them and a developer to design a custom woocomerce site and I currently manage the online store.</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://benchudyk.github.io/web/development/2014/07/15/project-6/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://benchudyk.github.io/web/development/2014/07/15/project-6/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Web</category>
        
        <category>Development</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yokohama</title>
        <description>While working for Fastsigns we were contracted to wrap cars for Yokohama. I designed and installed vinyl that would fit cars to spec. </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://benchudyk.github.io/print/2014/07/14/project-5/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://benchudyk.github.io/print/2014/07/14/project-5/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Print</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
